Somehow have unrestricted access to all
of the great pyramids of Egypt.
Whoa.
No.
This is the coolest
thing I've ever seen.
We'll be going into
the tombs of ancient pharaohs.
Passageway we're in leads to what
Egyptologists say is King Khufu's tomb.
The pharaoh who may have
ordered the pyramids to be built.
Whoa.
Hey.
This room is called the Grand Gallery.
What percentage of this pyramid do
you think we've seen so far?
We might never know
the answer to that question.
That's the coolest way
he could have answered that.
This next room, the highest point
in the largest ancient pyramid on Earth.
Woo.
That was awesome.
Before we go explore the other giant
pyramids, I wanna show
you guys base camp.
Yeah, this is nice.
We got a dinner table, some
tents to sleep in, and yo.
Wow.
Okay.
We even brought lights so you
could see the pyramids from camp.
That's gotta be the most
expensive nightlight that's ever existed.
This is the pyramid
we're gonna explore tomorrow.
I wanna start at 5am Everyone get some.
These pyramids were so technologically advanced
for their time that some credit them
to a pre Egyptian civilization, while some
point to even crazier theories, like aliens.
But Egyptologists are sure
that they were built
by the first Egyptians
as tombs for their kings.
And by the end
of this video, we're going
to find out which
of these theories is true.
All right, boys, I hope you're ready
to explore the next pyramid on our list.
The pyramid of Khafre.
What is special about this monstrosity?
Well, this pyramid is how we learn
how the casings of
each pyramid look like.
This is how they all
look like at some point.
That was right after
the aliens built them.
No aliens.
Rami led us nearly 100ft below
the Earth's surface,
deep into Khafre's pyramid.
This is a place where hardly anyone
in the modern world has ever been.
So to be honest, we had no
idea what to expect going down here.
The ancient Egyptians had cardboard.
We believe that this was the burial
chamber for King Khafre
for the longest time.
And now they're using it to store stuff.
Well, they're restoring
the pyramid, Jimmy.
They gotta use tools.
So that means there's
a real burial chamber.
Yes.
Rami actually took us
to the real resting place
thought to have once held
the body of King Khafre.
I see a big ceiling.
Whoa.