For challenge number one, you can temporarily
walk out of the Cube and attempt a free throw.
And if you make the shot, we will give a subscriber of
yours a free cybertruck and you'll be allowed back in the challenge.
But if you miss, your subscriber gets nothing
and you are eliminated.
How did they get this many cybertrucks in one place?
I cannot make that shot.
It's too risky.
Free throw is so easy.
Free throw is easy.
I could not have free throw to save
my life.
Everyone was on the edge trying to decide
if the first challenge was worth it.
But then Mark Rover did this.
Jimmy Peace.
I'm doing it.
No way.
Look at all the YouTubers in the background.
Oh, man, this is pressure.
This is a subscriber.
What's your name?
Matthew.
Don't let him down.
You gotta make this event.
I got faith in you.
It's on you, Mark.
Are you going to win your biggest fan a cybertruck,
or are you both leaving with nothing?